Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Greetings, Young Master and Second Young Master.
تحياتي، السيد الشاب والسيد الشاب الثاني.
These two are the experts Lord wishes to meet.
هذان هما الخبيران اللورد يرغب في لقاءهما.
Disciples of Master Bukku.
تلاميذ المعلم بوكو.
I am the Senior Brother from Yun Yin Mountain.
أنا الأخ الأكبر من جبل يون ين.
My name is Dongqing.
اسمي دونغ تشينغ.
This is my junior.
هذا هو صغيري.
Luobo.
لوبو.
Why would Father summon you?
لماذا يستدعيك الأب؟
You two...
انتما الاثنان...
This smell...
هذه الرائحة...
So filthy and foul.
قذرة وكريهة للغاية.
Go, go!
إذهب، إذهب!
You...
أنت...
General Huo, greetings.
تحياتي للجنرال هيو.
These two are masters from Yun Yin Mountain.
هؤلاء الاثنان هما أساتذة من جبل يون ين.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
We dare not call ourselves masters.
نحن لا نجرؤ على تسمية أنفسنا سادة.
But we truly are from the mountains.
ولكننا في الحقيقة من الجبال.
Earlier, due to an urgent situation,
في وقت سابق، بسبب حالة طارئة،
we accidentally injured the Second Young Master.
لقد أصبنا الشاب الثاني عن طريق الخطأ.
We hope for your forgiveness.
نرجوا مسامحتكم.
Our Second Young Master is merciful.
إن شابنا الثاني رحيم.
He showed restraint.
لقد أظهر ضبط النفس.
Otherwise, with your skills...
وإلا فمع مهاراتك...
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Lord, please slow down.
يا رب، من فضلك أبطئ.
Lord, are you alright?
يا رب هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I just caught a slight chill.
لقد شعرت بقشعريرة خفيفة.
Decades have passed in a flash.
لقد مرت عقود من الزمن في ومضة.
Dongqing has grown so much.
لقد نمت دونغشينغ كثيرًا.
Lord, you've met me before?
يا رب هل قابلتني من قبل؟
Your master
سيدك
often spoke of you before me.
لقد تحدثت عنك كثيرًا قبلي.
Seeing you today, you truly are talented.
عند رؤيتك اليوم، أنت موهوب حقًا.
Indeed, indeed.
بالفعل، بالفعل.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
And me, Lord?
وأنا يا رب؟
How did my master praise me?
كيف مدحني سيدي؟
And this is...
و هذه...
This is my junior, Luobo.
هذا هو صغيري، لوبو.
So rude, truly too rude.
وقح جدًا، وقح جدًا بالفعل.
Just two country bumpkins.
اثنين فقط من سكان الريف.
Young Master, don't stoop to their level.
سيدي الشاب، لا تنحدر إلى مستواهم.
If you really dislike them,
إذا كنت لا تحبهم حقًا،
I'll find a chance to deal with them.
سأجد فرصة للتعامل معهم.
You are far too rude.
أنت وقح للغاية.
Even Nan Zhengci, with such high martial arts,
حتى نان تشنغشي، مع مثل هذه الفنون القتالية العالية،
was injured by these two.
لقد أصيب من قبل هذين الاثنين.
With just you few...
فقط مع القليل منكم...
You should know your own limits.
يجب عليك أن تعرف حدودك الخاصة.
Yes.
نعم.
I am the dignified Young Master of Xuan City.
أنا السيد الشاب الكريم لمدينة شوان.
Of course, I must win people over with courtesy.
بالطبع، يجب عليّ أن أكسب الناس باللباقة.
To be honest,
صراحة،
we came this time
لقد جئنا هذه المرة
to look for our master.
للبحث عن سيدنا.
A month ago,
منذ شهر،
our master accepted your invitation
لقد قبل سيدنا دعوتك
and came to Xuan City to solve the strange illness.
وجاء إلى مدينة شوان لحل المرض الغريب.
He was to stay for half a month.
وكان من المقرر أن يبقى لمدة نصف شهر.
But until now,
ولكن حتى الآن،
there's been no news of our master.
لم ترد أي أخبار عن سيدنا.
We ask Lord to tell us
نطلب من الرب أن يخبرنا
where our master is now.
حيث سيدنا الآن.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Master Bukku was indeed entrusted by me
لقد تم تكليف السيد بوكو بالفعل من قبلي
to come to Xuan City and treat the epidemic.
للحضور إلى مدينة شوان ومعالجة الوباء.
However,
لكن،
one night, half a month ago,
في إحدى الليالي، منذ نصف شهر،
West Street was attacked by the Rotten.
تم مهاجمة شارع ويست من قبل الروتن.
Master Bukku went to help.
ذهب المعلم بوكو للمساعدة.
After that, he disappeared.
وبعد ذلك اختفى.
What?
ماذا؟
Disappeared?
اختفى؟
Then send people to search for him!
ثم أرسل الناس للبحث عنه!
We've searched the entire city.
لقد بحثنا في المدينة بأكملها.
But found no trace of the master.
ولكن لم يتم العثور على أي أثر للسيد.
Only this half note was found in his room.
تم العثور على نصف المذكرة فقط في غرفته.
Senior Brother Dongqing, please take a look.
الأخ الأكبر دونغ تشينغ، يرجى إلقاء نظرة.
The land of black and white hides mysteries.
أرض الأبيض والأسود تخفي أسرارًا.
Yin and Yang converge.
يتقارب الين واليانغ.
A clue emerges.
يظهر دليل.
The origin of the strange illness.
أصل المرض الغريب.
The Corrupted run rampant.
الفساد ينتشر بشكل كبير.
Chaos erupts at the Fire Sacrifice Ceremony.
اندلعت الفوضى في حفل التضحية بالنار.
The source of this matter remains unknown.
ويبقى مصدر هذه المسألة مجهولا.
Master Bukku must have discovered something.
يبدو أن المعلم بوكو قد اكتشف شيئًا ما.
Master Bukku and I share a deep friendship.
أنا والسيد بوكو تربطنا صداقة عميقة.
Now he has gone missing because of me.
والآن اختفى بسببي.
I feel deeply ashamed.
أشعر بالخجل الشديد.
Ashamed.
خجلان.
What's the use of feeling ashamed?
ما فائدة الشعور بالخجل؟
We don't even know if Master is alive or dead.
نحن لا نعلم حتى إذا كان المعلم حيًا أم ميتًا.
Mind your manners.
انتبه لأخلاقك.
Dongqing.
دونغتشينغ.
Your master often spoke of you to me.
لقد تحدث سيدك عنك معي كثيرًا.
He said you were gifted and clever.
لقد قال أنك موهوب وذكي.
The student surpasses the master.
الطالب يتفوق على المعلم
So,
لذا،
I want to ask for your help.
أريد أن أطلب مساعدتك.
Find the source of this strange illness.
ابحث عن مصدر هذا المرض الغريب
And completely eliminate the Corrupted.
والقضاء على الفاسدين نهائيا .
Alright, I promise.
حسنًا، أعدك.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Since Master
منذ المعلم
is connected to this illness,
يرتبط بهذا المرض،
then I believe
ثم اعتقد
if we uncover the truth,
إذا اكتشفنا الحقيقة،
we will surely find Master.
سوف نجد المعلم بالتأكيد.
General Huo.
الجنرال هوو
Dongqing, this child,
دونغ تشينغ، هذا الطفل،
you must keep a close eye on him for me.
يجب عليك مراقبته عن كثب من أجلي.
Yes, my Lord.
نعم سيدي.
I will watch him closely.
سأراقبه عن كثب.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Do we really have to examine the body at midnight?
هل يجب علينا فعلاً فحص الجثة في منتصف الليل؟
Midnight is when Yin and Yang shift, the purest time.
منتصف الليل هو الوقت الذي يتحول فيه الين واليانغ، وهو الوقت الأنقى.
It also helps us avoid attention.
ويساعدنا أيضًا على تجنب الاهتمام.
Two birds with one stone.
عصفورين بحجر واحد.
The corpse moved!
الجثة تحركت!
S-Senior Brother!
س-الأخ الأكبر!
Don't panic.
لا تُصب بالذعر.
After death,
بعد الموت،
gas expansion is normal.
تمدد الغاز أمر طبيعي.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Senior Brother, there really are ghosts!
أخي الأكبر، هناك أشباح حقا!
Let's get out of here.
دعونا نخرج من هنا.
Coward.
جبان.
Didn't expect the Second Young Master to investigate at this hour.
لم أتوقع أن يقوم الشاب الثاني بالتحقيق في هذه الساعة.
At midnight, the world is clear.
في منتصف الليل، يصبح العالم واضحا.
It's the best time to speak with the dead.
إنه أفضل وقت للتحدث مع الموتى.
These Corrupted are fake.
هذه الفاسدة مزيفة.
What?
ماذا؟
Fake?
مزيف؟
These Corrupted are different from last time.
هذه الفاسدة مختلفة عن المرة الماضية.
They're definitely not the same.
إنهم بالتأكيد ليسوا نفس الشيء.
I checked the records.
لقد قمت بفحص السجلات.
The previous Corrupted
الفاسد السابق
were rotten from skin to internal organs.
كانت فاسدة من الجلد إلى الأعضاء الداخلية.
Everything was decayed.
لقد كان كل شيء متحللا.
But this time,
ولكن هذه المرة،
their insides are intact.
أحشائهم سليمة.
Not only are they not rotten,
ليس فقط أنهم ليسوا فاسدين،
but on their limbs
ولكن على أطرافهم
there are stitching marks.
هناك علامات خياطة.
Also,
أيضًا،
the Corrupted at the Fire Sacrifice Festival
الفاسدون في مهرجان التضحية بالنار
have smooth teeth.
لديها أسنان ناعمة.
Unlike the people bitten to death before,
على عكس الأشخاص الذين عضّوا حتى الموت من قبل،
the wounds are different.
الجروح مختلفة
These Corrupted have ash in their nasal cavities.
هؤلاء الفاسدون لديهم رماد في تجاويف أنوفهم.
This shows that
وهذا يدل على أن
they were still breathing during the festival attacks.
كانوا لا زالوا يتنفسون أثناء هجمات المهرجان.
So that means
وهذا يعني
these fake Corrupted
هذه الفاسدة المزيفة
were alive during the ceremony.
كانوا على قيد الحياة أثناء الحفل.
This half-dead state
هذه الحالة نصف الميتة
is like being a living corpse.
كأنك جثة حية.
This...
هذا...
That's just too cruel.
هذا قاسي جدًا.
Master Dongqing
سيد دونغتشينغ
Come
يأتي
General Huo
الجنرال هوو
I personally prepared these vegetarian dishes for you both.
لقد قمت بإعداد هذه الأطباق النباتية لكما شخصيًا.
Thank you, General Huo.
شكرا لك يا جنرال هوو.
Please try them.
من فضلك جربهم.
Senior Brother
الأخ الأكبر
Have you understood Master’s words?
هل فهمت كلام المعلم؟؟؟
What does he mean by black and white, Yin and Yang?
ماذا يقصد بالأبيض والأسود والين واليانغ؟
What does it really mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك حقا؟
Black and white
الأسود والأبيض
It should refer to the Bagua diagram.
ينبغي أن يشير إلى مخطط باجوا.
According to Bagua theory,
وفقا لنظرية باجوا،
Qian represents Heaven.
تشيان يمثل السماء.
Kun represents Earth.
كون يمثل الأرض.
They are in the northwest and southwest directions.
وهم في الاتجاهين الشمالي الغربي والجنوب الغربي.
Yin and Yang merge.
ين و يانغ يندمجان.
There is Yin within Yang, and Yang within Yin.
هناك يين داخل يانغ، ويانغ داخل يين.
Yin and Yang unite.
يتحد الين واليانغ.
It should point to the intersection of Heaven and Earth.
ينبغي أن يشير إلى تقاطع السماء والأرض.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Be careful!
احرص!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why are you wearing my master’s Tiger Tooth?
لماذا ترتدي نمر سيدي؟؟؟
Senior Brother, catch the sword!
الأخ الأكبر، أمسك السيف!
It’s you.
إنه أنت.
Hero
بطل
I came to see you, Hero.
لقد جئت لرؤيتك يا بطل.
Young Master
السيد الشاب
You—what are you doing?
انت؟؟؟ماذا تفعل؟
Young Master! Young Master!
يا سيدي الشاب! يا سيدي الشاب!
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
So rude! Truly too rude.
يا لها من وقحة! وقحة جدًا حقًا.
My waist...
خصري...
Why are you all still standing there?
لماذا لا تزالون واقفين هناك؟
Go after them!
إذهب وراءهم!
No need.
لا حاجة.
With your abilities,
مع قدراتك،
even together, you’re no match for her.
حتى لو كنتما معًا، فأنتما لا تستطيعان منافسةً لها.
Hero
بطل
Hero, I’m scared.
بطل، أنا خائف.
I’m scared, Hero! Young Master!
أنا خائف يا بطل! يا سيدي الشاب!
Hero
بطل
Young Master
السيد الشاب
I’m scared.
انا خائفة.
Young Master! Young Master!
يا سيدي الشاب! يا سيدي الشاب!